

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Ruby on Rails
ReactJS
Javascript/jQuery/AJAX
HTML5/CSS3/Bootstrap
Postgres/MySQL
Heroku/Nginx/AWS
Git/Bitbucket
Jira/Trello
REST/AGILE/TDD
API Design/External Integration
Payment Gateway Implementation
Social Media Strategy
Ecommerce Strategy
Market Research
Growth Hacking

PERSONAL SKILLS

Always positive
Team player
Excellent communication
Extensive problem solving
Willing to take ownership
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Fast learner
Motivated

CONTACT

P: +1 647 290 9686 E: ikhakoo@gmail,com W: www.ikhakoo.com

IMRAN KHAKOO

WEB DEVELOPER & MARKETING EXPERT

ABOUT

I'm a Ruby on Rails developer, Internet Marketing Expert and former Network Administrator with over 7 years of professional experience. I have the ability and experience required to design and implement complex software projects for a diverse set of users.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERNET MARKETING + ECOMMERCE

Scripted Technologies Inc. | Dec 2016 - Present

- Manage over \$25,000 in marketing spend per month
- Develop marketing campaigns on various social media
- Increased revenue by 15% month over month
- Increased social media following and clicks by 200% month over month

RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER

Cambridge Brain Sciences | Jun 2016 - Present

- Developed web based platform for brain analysis tool
- Implementation of front-end using React JS
- Engaged with shaping development methodologies
- Participate in bi-weekly sprints and daily stand up meetings
- Lead role in implementation of payment solution (Stripe)
- Stack: Ruby on Rails, ReactJS, jQuery, AJAX, AWS, HTML5/CSS3/Bootstrap, MySQL, docker, GIT, Bitbucket, JIRA

RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER

Hashtagpaid Inc | Sep 2015 - Jun 2016

- Developed web based platform for Influencer Marketing
- Developed full test suite to ensure continuous deployment with use of Jenkins
- Participate in bi-weekly sprints and daily stand up meetings
- Lead role in implementation of payment solution (Stripe)
- Stack: Ruby on Rails, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, AWS, HTML5/CSS3/Bootstrap, Postgres, GIT, Trello

EDUCATION

BITMAKER LABS

Web Development Student | July 2015

THORNLEA S.S.

OSSD | June 2004